WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
The Three-Way
Deadlock Battle
Oh! Dad!
This isn't good!
Oh no, Gamatatsu!
Let's get out of here!
What? Why, why?
It doesn't matter, just hurry up!
Manda and Orochimaru,
Katsuyu and Tsunade...
They all bring back memories...
Shall we have a reunion
or something, Jiraiya?
Fool! I summon you after a long absence
and you make these boring jokes.
The time to conclude this long,
fateful confrontation has come.
I'm bringing Orochimaru down,
here and now!
Hey, Orochimaru...
Why'd you have to summon me
to a place like this?!
You... I'm going to eat you up!
Don't say that, Manda-sama...
You will be duly rewarded.
Who said I'm talking to you?!
Don't be so flippant, brat!
Hey, Orochimaru...
I expect you to prepare
a sacrificial offering of 100 people later.
Though Orochimaru-sama is
Manda's master,
if Manda learns that Orochimaru-sama
can't use Jutsu,
Manda will no doubt
double-cross him.
Despite the fact that he had
no other choice, in his condition,
it was too risky for Orochimaru-sama
to summon Manda.
Katsuyu... take that kid to Shizune!
Yes, ma'am.
All right! I can fight, too!
Shizune-sama, please take care of this child.
Naruto-kun...
Also, the battle is going to get
quite vicious from now.
Please go far away with my clone
and conceal yourself...
That's what Tsunade-sama wants.
Tsunade-sama...
You...
I'll hang you out until you're dry!
I've been wanting a snakeskin wallet...
Orochimaru,
you've sunk too deeply into vice!
We are no longer comrades.
Comrades?
That word makes me shiver.
Today is the last day that
we are called Sannin!
Acid Slime!
I'll start with this one!
Katsuyu!
Tsunade-sama...
Here they come!
I know!
Tsunade! Stay away!
Bunta! Give me some oil!
Okay!
Fire Style!
Toad Oil Flamethrower!
Humph... How's that?
Did it work?
No, that's...
Molten skin! He shed his skin!
Bunta! Under the earth!
What?!
It's the tail?!
Keep it shut!
They're Sannin, all right.
Dealing with two of them is rough.
Tsunade!
Well now, I can kill you
by wringing your neck.
My Chakra...
At this rate...
Even though you say
you won't die in battle,
you won't have a choice if
I rip your neck off...
Right, Tsunade?
How many minutes...
How many seconds can I hold on...?
I have to put it on the line!
Fine!
It's about time we put an end to this!
R-Ridiculous!
Not done yet!
Take this!
Damn it...!
Tsunade-sama... Not that...!
She's reached her limit...
No...
This guy...
I've hurled him around that much,
yet he's still...
So this is as far as you can go.
Shut up!
Don't rest!
Keep beating him.
This is the battle...
where I put my life on the line!
Orochimaru-sama!
I won't let you go!
You will stay with me until the end!
Take this!
I hit him and hit him.
Something's different...
What is it?
This... strange sense of discomfort?
However, with this...!
It's over!
He took a direct hit!
That was it.
Yeah...
Orochimaru-sama...
Putting me in this position!
I want to eat you and kill you,
but I can't even chew you up
with this hole in my mouth...
Next time, if we meet again,
be prepared!
Tsunade...
Even though you won't heal me,
I still have one way.
A way to resurrect these arms.
The Leaf Village...
I'll destroy it... without fail.
At that time, it would be nice
if we could meet again...
My comrades...
Tsunade and Jiraiya.
That face...?!
In some way or another,
he took someone else's body...?!
No wonder,
when we went at it a while ago,
I didn't get the same feeling
from him that I did in the past...
The true elixir of life.
That's my...
my immortality!
Some day, in the future...
Wait!
The bones in my ribs and feet
are broken...
The side effects of the Jutsu
are starting...
My body is... already...
Tsunade, you haven't changed.
You're no good at wagers.
Hokage is my dream!
I'll give you one week.
If you can master that Jutsu,
I'll acknowledge that you have
what it takes to become the Hokage...
and give you this necklace.
It's no joke!
If I have three days,
I'll master this Jutsu!
Men don't go back on their word!
I'm the grandson of the Hokage who
built the Village Hidden in Leaves, so...!
You said it.
Men don't go back on their word!
Right! I'll become just like Grandfather.
And the Hokage name will be mine!
Becoming Hokage is my dream!
I love this village and my comrades.
So I want to protect them.
An existence that protects everyone.
Becoming Hokage is my dream...
I'd like you... to take this.
Any time now, the side effects...
Tsunade-sama...
You...
It's nothing... If I rest a bit, I'll return
to my young form.
I'll rest in town.
And when Naruto wakes up,
We'll return to Leaf Village.
Tsunade...
Starting now, don't call me Tsunade.
Call me...
The Fifth Hokage?!
Granny Tsunade is
the Fifth Hokage starting today...
What, you look disgruntled, Naruto.
After all, compared to the old man,
the Third Hokage,
there's something...
rough-natured and kind of selfish...
loose with money, catty and stupid...
Somehow, I'm going to worry
if she can do it properly.
Tsunade-sama, would you like
to order something...
Moreover, a 50-year-old lady
transforming into a young lady...
Is it okay for the person who
will become Hokage
to lie to everyone, I wonder...?
Go outside, brat!
It's just like before...
Despite how I look,
I'm going to be the Fifth Hokage.
I shouldn't take
this short brat of a foe seriously...
This one is enough...
Don't call me brat!
I may be like this now,
but I'll be Hokage some day!
Here I go!
Another brow flick?!
Become a fine man...
and, a fine Hokage.
Yeah!
Okay! Shall we go home?
To our hometown the Leaf Village!
What? I haven't eaten yet...!
Don't try to distract me by laughing!
Nawaki... Dan...
the boy who will inherit your dreams,
my beloved ones,
is right here!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
Yahoo! Here we are
at a hot spring spot!
While Pervy Sage is gawking at women,
and Granny Tsunade is out somewhere,
I'm gonna relax and enjoy myself!
What?! Who worked over my room?!
I don't know who they are,
but I'm gonna find them
and kick their butts!
Next time:
"Naruto's Strange Hot Springs Side Trip."